<?xml version="1.0" ?>
 
<film>
  
<item>
  <Name>Marley</Name>
  <Genre>Music Documentary</Genre>
  <Summary>[ 2012, 144min, Dir: Kevin Macdonald, PG13 ] Bob Marley's universal appeal, impact on music history and role as a social and political prophet is both unique and unparalleled. MARLEY is the definitive life story of the musician, revolutionary, and legend, from his early days to his rise to international superstardom. Made with the support of the Marley family, the film features rare footage, incredible performances and revelatory interviews with the people that knew him best. From Academy Award-winning director Kevin Macdonald comes the story of a towering figure of musical history, whose music and message has transcended different cultures, languages and creeds to resonate around the world today as powerfully as when he was alive. </Summary>
  <Showtimes>9:45 Fri/Sat 6/22-23</Showtimes>
  <Admissions>$9 General or $5 wristband</Admissions>
  <website>http://magpicturescom/marley</website>
  </item>

 
  
  <item>
  <Name>Athens Burning</Name>
  <Genre>Music Documentary</Genre>
  <Summary> [ 2011, 108min, Dir: Andrew Haynes, NR ] A new, locally produced documentary centered around the history of the Georgia Theater in Downtown Athens. The film opens with the burning of the historic theater in summer, 2009, and chronologically covers the history of the Athens Music Scene from the 1970's through the present. Featuring interviews and performance footage from notable artists and musicians who performed at the venue over the decades, the film also documents the catastrophic fire, the fundraising efforts from the local community, and the re-construction of the theater. </Summary>
  <Showtimes>7:30 Fri/Sun 6/22,24</Showtimes>
  <Admissions>$5 General or Free w/ wristband</Admissions>
  <website>spherevibefilms.com</website>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <Name>Rock Doc Classic: Monterey Pop</Name>
  <Genre>Music Documentary</Genre>
  <Summary> 1968, 79min, Dir: D.A. Pennebaker, NR  Kick-off Your AthFestivities with a special showing of one of the Greatest Rock Documentaries Ever, MONTEREY POP, presented by 6X6 Media Arts Events. In addition to the usual 6X6 and Ciné fun (drinks, popcorn, door prizes) enjoy an introduction by esteemed guest speakerJOE SILVA, host of WUOG's Just Off The Radar. This classic concert film effectively sets the scene for the Monterey Pop Festival of 1967, which took place during the fabled "Summer of Love," when the hippie ethos was in its fullest flower, especially on the West Coast. Featured performers include Big Brother and the Holding Company with Janis Joplin, Jefferson Airplane, Hugh Masekela, Otis Redding, Ravi Shankar, The Mamas and the Papas, The Who and the Jimi Hendrix Experience. </Summary>
  <Showtimes>7:30 Wed/4:15 Sun</Showtimes>
  <Admissions>$5 General or Free w/ wristband</Admissions>
  <website>http://magpicturescom/marley</website>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <Name>Songs</Name>
  <Genre>Music Documentary</Genre>
  <Summary>[ 2011, 42min, Dir: Jennifer Formwalt, NR ] Through interview footage and live performances with local artists and musicians such as Dave Dowless, Hope for a Golden Summer, Creepy, Incendiaries, Puddin' Tang, Lysa Sullivan, The Jumpin' Jesus Christers, Kaitlin Jones, Tunabunny, The Buddy System, Athens Boys Choir, Poet Jeff Fallis, Mandy Jane, and Hola Halo, this documentary film explores creative life through a focus on the collaborative, traditional, and performative aspects of music, art, and culture.</Summary>
  <Showtimes>6:15 Fri/Sun 6/22, 6/24</Showtimes>
  <Admissions>$5 General or Free w/ wristband</Admissions>
  <website>http://vimeo.com/43573120</website>
  </item>
  
  <item>
  <Name>Emergent Heart</Name>
  <Genre>Music Documentary</Genre>
  <Summary>By a fortuitous twist of fate, a budding director, a dance troupe, and a recording collective/philanthropy came together, to produce a modern dance video for the lead single off the forthcoming EMERGENT HEART full length. At 7:30p, meet the contributors, dancers, and director during a social hour in the CineLab, with music by Young Benjamin. At 8pm sharp, get an exclusive first look at the video "Top Shelf".</Summary>
  <Showtimes>7:30p Wed 6/20</Showtimes>
  <Admissions>Free</Admissions>
  <website></website>
  </item>
  
<item>
<Name>A Fighting Chance</Name>
<Genre>Character Documentary</Genre>
<Summary> [ 2010, 90min, Dir: Takashi Doscher and Alex Shofner, NR ] A vivid, character-driven documentary following the inspiring story of Kyle Maynard, born with only three major joints: a neck and two shoulders. Not only has he learned to live life independently and without prosthetics, Kyle has plans to fight in an official Mixed Martial Arts match – a highly controversial and dangerous goal.      
</Summary>
<Showtimes>9:30p Wed 6/20</Showtimes>
<Admissions>$5 General or Free w/ wristband</Admissions>
<website>http://fightingchancemovie.com</website>
</item>

     
  </film>
	
  

